m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Nonopig  芒果妖怪  紫玉  阿好  天朝直属
时间轴：烟幕迟迟   擦擦   校对：阿好
特效&后期：灰灰是菇凉   总监：阿好
你被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
联系系统管理员
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
身份不明
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
身份不明
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
政府认为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
关键执行人
我们不
We don't.
失踪
关键执行人
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
状态：纽约警局任职
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第二季 第十三集
-唐纳利特工  停车  -你是谁
- Agent Donnelly, stop your car. - Who is this?
我是你后座的男人的搭档
I'm the partner of the man in your back seat.
我收到情报
I have a source that tells me
你现在正处于极度危险中
you're in grave danger.
你好  爱人  想我了吗
Hey, lover. Miss me?
3个未接来电
请接电话  警探
芬奇
Finch.
警探  你没事吧
Detective, are you all right?
我们遭到伏击
We were ambushed.
她杀了唐纳利  带走了约翰
She killed Donnelly and took John.
你受伤了吗
Are you injured?
没  但我被铐住了
No, I'm just handcuffed.
集中精神
You have to focus now.
找到钥匙
Find the keys.
好的  等等
Okay, wait. W-w-wait.
喂
Hello?
警探  有人看到你跟约翰和唐纳利特工一起吗
Detective, did anyone see you with John and Agent Donnelly?
应该没有
I don't think so.
那你马上离开  立刻
Then you need to get out of there now.
我不能逃离犯罪现场  芬奇
I can't just flee a crime scene, Finch.
我明白  乔丝
I understand, Joss,
但你不走  情况会更复杂
but things will get a lot more complicated if you don't.
芬奇  那个伏击我们的女人
Listen, Finch, the woman who ambushed us,
我认为是他在中情局的搭档
I think it was his partner from the CIA,
就是斯诺说死了的那个
the one that Snow said was dead.
芬奇
Finch!
是  我知道她是谁
Yes, I'm aware of who she is.
赶紧走  警探
Now go, Detective.
卡拉・斯坦顿  你想干什么
Kara Stanton. What is it that you want?
欢迎回来  约翰
Welcome back, John.
卡拉
Kara.
我还以为你
I thought you were--
死了
Dead?
我可不擅长死
I wasn't very good at it.
当然  你也一样
Of course, neither were you.
不过  这位派我们杀害彼此的朋友
Our friend here, on the other hand, who sent us to kill each other,
我觉得他特别擅长死
I suspect he'll be great at it.
-约翰  -马克
- John. - Mark.
跟我一样啊
Looks just like mine.
欢迎加入
Welcome to the party.
我认得那表情  约翰
I know that look you get, John.
在你轻举妄动之前
Right before you do something disruptive.
你也许不在乎自己
You may not care about yourself,
但你身上绑着的塑性炸药量
but you've got enough semtex duct-taped to you
足以殃及池鱼
to spread a lot of misery around.
在你想要拆除炸弹背心前
And before you think about disarming that vest...
记住  我给你们俩设置了快速拨号
just remember I've got you both on speed dial.
这是要干什么呢  卡拉
So what's this about, Kara?
我只想让我们重温一次
I thought I'd get us all back together
一起出外勤的时光
for one last little bit of field work
重温旧梦
for old time's sake.
你可没这么情意深长
You were never that sentimental.
我没有吗
I wasn't, was I?
你和马克得帮我做点事
You and Mark are gonna run a few errands for me.
如果按时完成任务
Execute your tasks in a timely manner
你们就会平安无事
and you will remain intact.
这到底是为什么事
So what's this really about?
为了新世界中三位已死去的小间谍
This is about three dead little spies in a brave new world.
为了另一个世界  约翰
It's about the afterlife, John,
我们能有容身之处
and us negotiating our places in it.
-喂  -终于找到你了
- Hello? - There you are.
你不接手机了吗
You don't answer your cell anymore?
我  手机丢了
I, uh, lost it.
有事吗
What's up?
早上接到报案
A call came in this morning.
有位联调局特工被枪杀
An FBI agent was found shot.
是唐纳利
It was Donnelly.
他死了  卡特
He's dead, Carter.
发生什么事了
What happened?
联调局的人正在查呢
The feds are trying to find that out.
他们要找你
They're asking for you.
他们说了为什么吗
They say why?
他们知道你和他一起在查案
They knew you two were working a case together.
我马上过来
I'm on my way.
我们那位朋友有消息吗
Have you heard from our mutual friends?
怎么了
Why?
眼镜男昨晚让我去
Glasses sent me out looking
找你和神奇小子
for you and Wonder Boy last night.
说是情况紧急
Said it was some kind of emergency.
掉了只耳环吗
Lose an earring?
还真是
Guess I did.
打扰了  你是卡特警探吗
Excuse me, are you Detective Carter?
是我
Yes.
联调局特工摩斯
SAIC Moss.
-能跟你谈谈吗  -当然
- Talk to you a minute? - Sure.
你最后一次见唐纳利特工是什么时候
When was the last time you saw Special Agent Donnelly?
昨天在里克岛监狱
Yesterday at Rikers.
他昨天有什么异常之处吗
Anything out of the ordinary with him?
看上去是否很烦恼
He seem concerned or troubled?
没有  怎么了
No. Why?
那个案子  西装男
That case, your suit guy.
唐纳利花了很多时间查他
Donnelly was spending a lot of time on him.
他似乎很确定你们追的这个人
Seemed convince this guy you were chasing
以前在政府工作过
had backing inside the government.
他跟你说过吗
He mention that to you?
应该没有
Not that I can recall.
局里的长官担心他
The superiors at the bureau were concerned
有点偏执了
he was getting paranoid.
担心他丧失客观性
That he might have lost his perspective.
你怎么想
What do you think?
我想唐纳利是个好特工
I think Donnelly was a good agent.
感谢你对我们的帮助  警探
I appreciate your assistance on this, Detective.
保持联系
I'll be in touch.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
你确定
You sure?
打算告诉我是怎么回事吗
You wanna tell me what's going on?
我不知道我能不能
I don't know if I can.
但我知道有人应该能
But I know someone who might.
卡拉・斯坦顿的工作经历
Kara Stanton's work history,
化名  先前住址  财务报告
aliases, prior addresses, financial records,
以及她的死亡证明
and her death certificate.
遗憾的是  最重要的那一部分
Unfortunately, the most relevant part of her life
我们知之甚少
is the one we know the least about.
她被宣布死亡后的生活
After she was declared dead.
斯诺也认识斯坦顿
Snow knew Stanton too.
那次他闯进那家科技公司  我追上他时
When I caught up with him after he broke into that tech company,
他提到了一个女人
he mentioned a woman.
说她在计划什么大事
Said she was planning something big.
他去那家科技公司  到底是找什么呢
What was it he was looking for at the technology company?
他偷了一块硬盘
He stole a hard drive.
我需要报告中
I'm gonna need everything you know
有关硬盘的一切
about that drive from your report.
帮助里瑟先生的唯一办法
The only way we can help Mr. Reese
就是想办法找出
is to try to figure out
她的计划是什么  她在为谁办事
what she's planning to do and for whom.
我看到斯诺的时候  他身上捆着炸弹背心
Well, when I saw Snow, he was wired with a bomb vest.
我想现在可以确定的是  不论约翰在哪里
I guess it's fair to say that wherever John is,
他肯定亟需我们的帮助
he needs our help and quickly.
我们要见什么人
Who are we meeting?
这个不用操心
Don't worry about it.
你们拿点东西就行了
You're just picking something up.
进不进来啊
You coming in or what?
你们是黑警
You guys dirty cops?
联邦探员
Feds?
我猜是联邦探员
I'm guessing feds.
有我们要的东西吗
Do you have what we came for?
已经准备好了
Good to go.
按你们老板的要求格式化了
Formatted to your boss's specifications.
像这么高端的政府设备很少见
I don't see many high-end government rigs like this one.
你们老板  她肯定背景很深
Your boss, she must have very deep pockets.
把硬盘给我们
Let's have the drive.
要价再加五万块
The price has gone up another $50,000.
还价
Make a counteroffer.
扭断他脖子
Break his neck.
我相信你已经收过钱了
I believe you've been paid already.
我相信你们听到我的要价了
I believe you have my price.
杀了他  约翰
Kill him, John.
不行
No.
行
Okay.
那我就  把东西留着了
I'll just, uh, hang on to it then.
也许看看有什么用
Maybe see what I can get for it.
去拿硬盘  然后走人
Now get the drive and get moving.
还有  约翰
And, John?
这是最后一次警告
That's your last warning.
我们确信五角大楼里有人
We believe someone inside the pentagon
把一台含源代码的电脑卖给了一家中国公司
sold a secure laptop to a Chinese firm.
我们得拿回电脑
We need the laptop returned.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
鄂尔多斯
Ordos.
这是中国中部的一个企业开发区
It's a company town in the middle of China.
里瑟  还有件事
Reese, one more thing.
你拿到程序包之后
After you secure the package,
清除斯坦顿特工
you are to retire agent Stanton.
她叛变了
She's been compromised.
你让我杀了我的搭档吗
You're telling me to kill my partner?
发现你没加入我们小小的东方之旅
Noticed you're not joining us on our little far east getaway.
这次的工作必须由两个人完成
This one's strictly a two-man job and for good reason.
最近几个月  我们发现
Over the past couple of months, it has come to our attention
里瑟探员叛变了
that Agent Reese has been compromised.
作为他的搭档
And as his partner--
你要我除掉他吗
You want me to take him out?
我们要自己清理门户  卡拉
We clean up our own mess, Kara.
我会处理的
I'll take care of it.
该结束了  约翰
Time to wrap this up, John.
听着  卡拉
Listen, Kara--
对不起  约翰
Sorry, John.
他们告诉我你已经叛变了
They told me you'd been compromised.
我接到了相同的命令
I got the same orders as you.
-可以发射了  -发射
- You are clear to engage. - Engaging.
很好  你醒了
Good. You're awake.
我在哪里
Where am I?
这是另一个世界  亲爱的
You're in the afterlife, my dear.
我不会开口的
I won't talk.
我也不想你开口
I wouldn't want you to.
你需要休息
You need rest.
而且  我知道你的名字  斯坦顿女士
Besides, I already know your name, Ms. Stanton.
事实上  我知道关于你的一切
In fact, I know almost everything about you.
你来自哪里  为谁工作
Where you're from, who you work for.
你如何沦落至此
How you ended up in that bed.
我玩的是情报
Information is my business.
这是你的政府派你找的东西
This is what your government sent you to find.
他们迫切想要毁掉的东西
Something they were so eager to destroy
甚至不惜连你也一起杀掉
that they were willing to kill you too.
你知道这是什么吗
Do you know what it is?
答案  可以解答一个非常有趣的问题
An answer to a very interesting question.
想知道这个问题是什么吗
Would you like to know what that question is?
我不关心
I don't care.
你不关心  是吧
No, you don't, do you?
所以你我会相处愉快的
That's why you and I are gonna get along.
你应该吃点东西  约翰
You should eat something, John.
过了这村就没这店了
You may not get another chance.
我不太有食欲
I don't have that much of an appetite.
马克一开始也是这样
Mark was like you at first.
我半死不活在东胜一家医院醒来时也是这样
So was I when I woke up half-dead in a hospital in Dongsheng.
无法掌控身边的一切
You can't control anything around you.
就只能用最微不足道的法子反击
So you fight back in whatever little ways you can.
比如说绝食
Like refusing to eat.
但最终  会接受命运
But in time, you accept your fate
就像这位马克
like Mark here...
吃个汉堡
and have a hamburger.
我只是不饿  卡拉
I'm just not that hungry, Kara.
不过等到我反击的时候  你会知道的
But when I do fight back, you'll know it.
有什么好笑的吗  马克
Something funny, Mark?
你们都是损坏品
You're both damaged goods.
让你们自相残杀岂止高效
Having the two of you take each other out wasn't just efficient,
简直美妙
it was poetic.
那为什么还用巡航导弹
So why the cruise missile?
确保万无一失
Had to be sure.
那你觉得效果怎么样呢
And how's that working out for you?
下次见
See you next time, huh?
该你们干活了
That's your cue.
吧台那里的人
The men at the counter.
跟出去
Follow them outside.
偷走他们的车
You're going to steal their car.
人家肯定会表示反对
Pretty sure they'll object to that.
那就让他们改变主意
So change their minds.
要用我的方法来解决吗
Or should I deal with them my way?
伙计
Hey, fellas?
有空吗
You got the time?
够了
That's enough.
我说够了
I said enough.
卡拉的游戏我奉陪
I'll play along with Kara's little game.
但不能杀害平民
But killing civilians isn't going to be a part of it.
明白吗
Clear?
好吧  约翰
Fine, John.
你有何建议
What do you suggest?
这家伙带着武器
This guy's carrying.
他们是烟酒火器管理局特工
They're ATF agents.
你们现在也是了
And now you are too.
你们就要接到临时任务了
You're being temporarily reassigned.
接电话  约翰
Answer the phone, John.
放聪明点  否则我保证
But be smart or I'll make it impossible
你和马克会尸骨无存
for anyone to tell where you end and Mark begins.
怎么
Yep?
贝克  莫瑟尔街780号有情况
Baker, we've got a situation developing over at 780 Mercer.
你和路易斯去看看
Need you and Louis to check it out.
就去
Will do.
两位可以去干活了
Time for you boys to go to work.
穿好制服  扔掉电话
Take the jackets, lose the phones.
信息发送成功
我们会救回他  小熊
We'll get him back, Bear.
我保证
I promise.
请讲  警探
Yes, Detective?
斯诺从藤真科技偷的硬盘
So the hard drive Snow stole from Fujima
只有一小批货
is from a small batch.
型号是DH950
Model number DH-950.
安全局授权的
It's NSA certified.
这个型号是专为
This model is made exclusively
政府部门和军队生产的
for government and military installations.
斯坦顿要它做什么
What would Stanton want with it?
要我猜的话
If I had to guess,
肯定是为了存储一些极度敏感或危险的信息
it's to store something highly sensitive or dangerous.
我刚接到了一条来自陌生号码的短信
Listen, I've just received a text from an unfamiliar number.
写了UXO
It reads "UXO".
UXO是军用代码
"UXO" is the military designation
指装有未爆品
for unexploded ordinance.
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese.
他可能穿着炸弹背心
He could be wearing a bomb vest.
我把号码发给你
Sending you the number.
你追踪一下
You need to track down the location
信息发送地点  警探
it was sent from, Detective.
这就去
I'm on it.
疏散这个区域
Clear this area!
尽快封锁街道
Lock down the street as soon as you can.
快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on.
所有人马上离开这里
Need everyone out of here right now!
我知道咱们是来处理什么事了
I think I know what kind of situation we're responding to.
炸弹威胁
Bomb threat.
无法抗拒
Couldn't resist.
靠你们的伪装进入大楼
Now use your cover to get inside the building.
去乘电梯
Go to the elevators.
右后方第一部电梯
Get in the right rear one.
等一下  伙计们
Hold on, fellas.
防爆小组已经接管这里  他们
Bomb squad's running the show. They go--
我们不用听防爆小组的
We don't answer to the bomb squad.
怎么说呢  这是标准流程
What can I tell you? It's SOP.
你知道半公斤塑性炸药
You know what just a half pound of semtex
会对这栋楼和里面的人造成何等危害吗
can do to a building like this or the people in it?
-不  但我接到  -我知道
- No, but I got-- - Well, I do.
你耽误的时间越久
And the longer you delay us,
就越有可能亲身体会到
the more likely it is you're gonna find out.
让开
Now get out of the way.
警探  你找到他们了吗
Detective, did you find them?
没  不过他们来过
No, but they were here.
他们跟着另外两个人出去了
They followed two other men out.
发短信的电话是
It turns out the phone that sent the text
烟酒火器管理局探员的
belongs to an ATF agent.
他和搭档刚被派去处理
He and his partner were just called
莫瑟尔街780号的炸弹威胁
to a bomb threat at 780 Mercer.
炸弹威胁
A bomb threat?
那是栋办公楼  警探
It's an office building, Detective.
里面主要是商业和企业租户
Mostly commercial and corporate tenants.
不  这个有意思
No, this is interesting.
怎么
What is?
那栋楼有21层
The building has 21 floors,
但楼层指南只有20层
but the directory only lists 20.
21层被静水进口公司租下了
21st floor is registered to a Stillwater Imports.
然而静水进口公司没有
Except Stillwater Imports doesn't appear to have
进行任何商业活动
any ongoing business activity.
这是家空壳公司
This is a shell corporation.
我会继续查
I'll keep looking into it,
不管斯坦顿在找什么
but whatever Stanton's after,
肯定在那里
I bet it's in there.
你们要去21层
You're going to the 21st floor.
电梯只到20层
The elevator only goes to 20.
用输入面板
The access pad.
输入密码051573
Enter this code: 051573.
上面有什么
What's up there?
21层是五级国防部设施
The 21st floor is a level 5 DOD facility.
很遗憾  那里的守卫
Unfortunately, the men guarding it
不会因炸弹威胁这种家常便饭而离开
won't leave it for something as routine as a bomb threat.
他们看到你们肯定不会高兴的
And they're not gonna be very happy to see you boys.
该死  卡拉
Damn it, Kara.
算了吧  约翰  你就不怀念吗
Come on, John. Didn't you miss this?
咱们三人一起工作的时光
The three of us working together?
我们要对付的是什么人
What are we looking at?
要我猜的话
If I had to guess,
两个三角洲部队成员拿着M4步枪
two delta force operators with M-4s
只要电梯门未经授权打开就会
trained to fire if those elevator doors open
毫不犹豫地开火
without authorization.
用三角洲部队做守卫
Delta force for guards?
我们这是在哪儿
Where the hell are we?
高级叛逃者的安全屋吗
Safe house for high-level defectors?
也许是生化武器实验室
Bioweapons lab maybe.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
我说什么来着
What did I say?
他们一旦脱身就会杀了我们
These guys get free, they're gonna kill us.
他们只是履行职责  我不认识他们
They're just doing their job and I don't know them.
这里我唯一确定该死的人是你
The only person here I'm pretty sure deserves to die is you.
看来你确实变了  约翰
I guess you have changed, John.
希望你的道德感不会把我们害死
I hope your conscience doesn't get us killed.
够了
Enough.
下一步要抓紧时间了  先生们
Time is a factor in this next stage, gentlemen.
这设施里可能会有些信号干扰
And there may be some signal interference inside the facility,
因此我要稍微改变下你们的激励机制了
so we'll have to change your incentives a little bit.
早上好
Good morning.
我本打算打开英语字幕
I was going to have them turn on the English captions,
不过我想起来  你的普通话很好
but then I remembered you're fluent in Mandarin.
你国家安全部的老板
Don't your bosses at the Ministry of State Security
就没有更好的事给你做了吗
have anything better for you to do?
亲爱的  你认为我为政府工作
My dear, if you think I work for the government,
我真得炒了我的裁缝了
I really must fire my tailor.
那你是为谁工作
Then who do you work for?
你在美国海军学院读过经典著作  卡拉
You read the classics at Annapolis, Kara.
还记得[希腊神话]泰坦吗
Do you recall the Titans?
旧神
The old gods?
他们惧怕新神
They were so afraid of the new gods--
他们的孩子
their own children--
于是就吃掉他们
that they ate them.
你为旧神工作  卡拉
You work for the old gods, Kara.
他们背叛了你
And they betrayed you.
他们想杀掉你
They were willing to kill you...
因为他们惧怕
because they're afraid.
他们隐约知道要发生什么了
They have an inkling of what happens next.
既然你不是为国安部工作  那你来这里干嘛
If you don't work for the MSS, then why are you here?
因为和中情局不一样
Because unlike the CIA,
我的组织认为你非常有用
my organization still thinks you could be very useful.
你觉得我会为你工作
You think I'd work for you?
扭断你脖子  我是不是就能继续看电视了
If I break your neck, can I go back to watching TV?
不  卡拉
No, Kara.
我知道你不会为我们工作
I know you wouldn't work for us.
不会为了钱
Not for money.
就像我说的  我玩的不是钱
But as I said, money is not my business.
我能给你提供你的旧东家无法给你
I can offer you what your old employers couldn't
也不愿给你的东西
or wouldn't give you.
我能给你答案
I can give you an answer.
你开口问就行了
You merely have to tell me the question.
谁
Who?
是谁害的我
Who did this to me?
严格说来
Precisely,
不是你的老上司  马克・斯诺
not your old boss, Mark Snow.
我都能想象出你对他的报复计划了
I have a fairly graphic idea of your plans for him.
但真正应该承担责任的人
But the person truly responsible.
是一开始卖掉这台电脑的人
The person who sold the laptop in the first place.
要我拿什么交换
In exchange for what?
你还记得
Do you remember...
泰坦是怎么灭亡的吗
how the Titans were finally killed?
在他们吃掉最小的孩子宙斯之前
Before they could eat their youngest child, Zeus,
用他的襁褓裹了一块石头
they wrapped a boulder in his swaddling clothes,
看着他的父亲被噎住
then watched as his father choked on it.
我们就位了
We're in position.
第一个目标是值班室
The first thing you'll hit is the security desk.
拿下摄像头  警报器
Take out the cameras, alarms,
清除备份里最后两小时的影像
and erase the last two hours on the backups.
我会告诉你们接下来怎么走
I'll tell you where to go from there.
无信号
我们进来了
We're in.
问题是进来哪儿了
In what is the question.
你们要找一名
You're looking for a technician
有高级许可的技术员
with high-level clearance.
试试找标着"应用研究"的恒温室
Try the temperature-controlled room labeled "Applied Research"
走  我们走  伙计们
Go. Let's go, folks.
到处找不到他们
I don't see them anywhere.
肯定已经上去了
Must already be up there.
卡特
Carter.
警探  你好
Detective, hello.
我找到了机密楼层的信息
I have information on your restricted floor.
我听不清
I can barely hear you.
抱歉噪音很大
Sorry about the noise,
但我需要有更好匿名无线网络的地方
but I had to relocate to a place with better Wi-Fi anonymity
才好黑进国防部
before hacking the Department of Defense.
你黑进了国防部
You hacked the DOD?
静水进口公司是
Stillwater Imports is a cover
其网络安全控制中心的掩护
for their cyber security operations center.
那是什么
What is that?
台面上他们是监控和保护
Officially their role is to monitor and protect
敏感的政府网络不受网络恐怖主义影响
sensitive government networks against cyber terrorism.
私底下呢
And unofficially?
他们在研制攻击软件武器
They're developing weaponized malware
像震网病毒或火焰病毒
like Stuxnet and Flame.
你也许记得它们被用于
You may recall they were used
破坏伊朗核离心机
to sabotage Iranian nuclear centrifuges.
-网络战  -是的
- Cyber warfare. - Yes.
等等
Wait.
所以斯坦顿需要硬盘
That's why Stanton needed the hard drive.
为什么
Why?
她要让他们窃取网络武器
She's gonna have them steal a cyber weapon.
拿到后  她为之工作的人
With that, the people that she's working for
可以关闭整个国家的电网
could shut down a country's power grids,
瘫痪通信  甚至更糟
cripple their communications, or worse.
我们得阻止她  警探
We're gonna have to stop her, Detective.
我正在努力
I'm working on it.
我们得上到那层
We gotta get up to that floor.
你觉得防爆小组的小子们能让咱们过去吗
You think the bomb squad boys are gonna go for that?
那祝你好运
Good luck.
我们就说
We'll just tell 'em
是来协助清查楼梯的
we're gonna help 'em clear the stairs.
什么  等等  那可有20层啊
What? Wait, that's 20 floors.
21层
21.
就是那里
That's it.
我是对的
I was right.
生化武器实验室
Bioweapons lab.
不是生化  是电子
Not bio. Electronic.
那房间是敏感信息隔间设备
That room's a SCIF.
能防止无线电信号
Built to keep any wireless or radio signals
传入或传出
from getting in or out.
你们交的税用上了
Your tax dollars at work.
进去那个房间
You need to get into that room.
然后交给马克负责
Mark can take it from there.
那里面有什么  卡拉
What's in there, Kara?
进去就行了  别磨蹭
Just get inside and don't drag your feet.
否则你就引爆吗
Or you'll detonate?
你引爆  你的计划也要跟我们陪葬
You do and you'll blow up your plan along with us.
我喜欢你  约翰
Fond as I am of you, John,
可别要我提醒你  你是可损耗品
don't make me remind you just how expendable you are.
明天见  吉米
See you tomorrow, Jimmy.
我们需要你加会儿班
We're gonna need you to put in some overtime.
安静
Quiet.
-你们是谁  -兄弟
- Who are you? - Hey, bud.
你们知道自己在哪里吗
Do you guys have any idea where you are?
搭把手  行吗
Just give us a hand, would you?
登陆
Log in.
去拿硬盘
Get the drive.
马克  我们不是一定要做
Mark, we don't have to do this.
就是  不做就得死
Yes, we do or we're dead.
不  这里没信号
No, there's no signal.
她听不见
She can't hear us.
我们能想到法子阻止她
We can figure out a way to stop her
或至少取下炸弹背心
or at least a way out of these vests.
我试过了
I've tried.
-没办法  -肯定会有
- There isn't one. - well, there has to be.
我们没时间了
We don't have time.
-带他去服务器  -这边
- Show him the servers. - This way.
我查出硬盘接口就通知你
I'll let you know when I find a bay for the drive.
-你叫什么名字  -凯文
- What's your name? - Kevin.
我会想办法让我们都活着出去  凯文
I'm gonna try to get us out of this alive, Kevin.
但我需要你的帮助
But I'm gonna need your help.
喂
Hello?
-是我  -里瑟先生
- It's me. - Mr. Reese.
时间有限  我现在在一处国防部设施中
I don't have much time. I'm in a DOD facility.
我收到你的信息了  她要你做什么
I got your text. What is she having you do?
偷个东西吧
Stealing something, I think.
她似乎想偷一件网络武器
I think she may be aiming to steal a cyber weapon.
网络武器
Cyber weapon?
那些盘里有什么
What's on these drives?
凯文
Kevin...
我们要想撑过这关  你必须相信我
If we're gonna survive this, you need to trust me.
网络信息战部队
Information warfare units.
病毒  蠕虫  军事级别的攻击软件
Viruses, worms, military-grade malware
用来感染摧毁敌军电脑网络的
designed to infect and destroy enemy computer networks.
所以这些机子都没联网
That's why these machines aren't networked.
是的  这里的一切都不允许外传
Yes, nothing in here can be allowed to get out there.
她应该在找一个程序  代号"天鹅座"
She may be looking for a project with a code name "Cygnus".
"天鹅座"在哪里
What is Cygnus?
那是新型超级病毒
It's a new super virus.
如果误入敌手  能毁掉大部分民用网络
In the wrong hands it could cripple major civilian networks,
我们自己的防御系统  甚至整个因特网
our own defense systems, even kill the entire internet.
也就是说  可以用来关掉机器
Which means it could be used to shut down the machine.
我不会允许的
I won't let that happen.
哈罗德  我要你离这里远点儿
Harold, I need you to stay clear of the building.
你要做什么
What are you going to do?
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese?
有没有办法清空那些盘
Is there a way to erase these drives?
除非系统出现安全漏洞
Only if there's a security breach to the system.
失效保护功能就会洗掉硬盘
Then its failsafe is to wipe the drives.
检测到安全漏洞
启动数据控制  清空全部盘
你干什么
What are you doing?
在她染指前毁掉"天鹅座"
Destroying Cygnus before she gets her hands on it.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你会害死我们  约翰
You're gonna get us killed, John.
走着瞧
We'll see.
把盘放回去
Put that drive back in.
不可能
Not gonna happen.
启动
别闹了  孩子们
Break it up, boys.
卡拉
Kara.
我知道你不会乖乖听命的  约翰
I knew you wouldn't follow orders, John.
就像在鄂尔多斯一样
Just like in Ordos.
-你胆怯了  -你来晚了
- You lost your nerve. - You're too late.
我已经清空了硬盘
I erased the drives.
启动安全清空完成
你永远都看不清大局  是吧约翰
Never were one for the bigger picture, were you, John?
我只需要你们帮我扫清障碍
All I wanted was for you two to clear a path for me.
干得不错
Nicely done.
拿上硬盘
Get the drive.
走
Let's go.
看  我并不想从这里取走什么
See, I'm not looking to take anything from this place.
这些都已经落后一代了
These boys are at least a generation behind.
插入硬盘
无意冒犯
No offense.
我只想送他们点东西
I'm more interested in giving them something.
这房间是干什么的
What is this room?
我们用来监控
Where we monitor
政府最高安全网络抵抗网络攻击
the government's most secure networks against cyber attacks.
她从这里可以访问到
From here she could reach--
一切
Everything.
启动上传
你干了什么  卡拉
What have you done, Kara?
干我的工作  约翰
My job, John.
卡拉  听着
Kara, listen.
我明白你的感受
I know how you feel.
我当时也在鄂尔多斯  记得吗
I was in Ordos too, remember?
没错  我们被伤害了  背叛了
And, yes, we were burned, betrayed...
上传完成
但我们活下来了
But we survived.
放手吧
You've gotta let it go.
还不晚
It's not too late.
你可以终止这一切
You can end this.
约翰
John.
我正有此意
I plan to.
我之前说的是真的
I meant what I said before.
我怀念这个
About missing this.
但他们说的是对的
But it's true what they say.
你已无法再回家
You can't go home again.
别了 各位
So long, fellas.
你能不能控制开门
Can you override the door?
不能
No.
但我可以让房间的能量供应超负荷
But I can overload the room's power supply
应该能造成紧急停机
which should cause an emergency shutdown.
还锁着
Still locked.
肯定是备用电源启动了
Battery backup must have kicked in.
在这边
Over here.
待在原地
Stay put.
我们追不上她了
We'll never catch up with her.
我们要远离平民
We need to get clear of any civilians.
我们可以上楼顶
We can get up to the roof--
上帝啊  里瑟
God, Reese.
这套自我牺牲精神
The whole self-sacrifice bit
已经有点过时了  不是吗
beginning to wear a little thin, don't you think?
局里有间安全屋  就在两条街外
Agency's got a safe house less than two blocks from here.
机会不大  但我别无他选了
It's a long shot, but it's all I got.
就算你赶到了
Even if you made it,
你以为局里会再接受你吗
you think the agency would take you back?
在他们眼里  你已经叛变了
In their eyes, you're compromised.
想想吧
Think about it.
等待你的只有黑布罩头
All that's waiting for you is a black hood.
祝你好运  约翰
Good luck, John.
-约翰  -卡特
- John! - Carter.
你们得马上离开
You need to get off this floor right now.
不  我们要帮你取下炸弹背心
No, we need to get you out of that vest.
-不行的  -我在伊拉克见过很多
- You can't. - I saw enough of them in Iraq.
带她离开
Get her out of here.
约翰  拜托听我说
John, please listen to me--
没时间了
There's no time.
你有太多不能舍弃的
You've got too much to lose.
不  约翰  不要这么做
No, John, you are not doing that.
莱奈尔
Lionel?
-卡特  他是对的  -放开我
- Carter, he's right. - Get off of me.
想想你儿子
Think of your son.
约翰
John.
不要这么做
You don't have to do this.
你知道我必须
You know I do.
换你也会做同样的事
Because you'd do the exact same thing.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你们
Both of you.
来  卡特  我们走  来
Come on, Carter, let's go. Come on.
看来我没迟到
So I see I'm not too late.
我早该知道你会来
I should have known you'd turn up here.
我告诉过你离远点儿
I told you to stay clear.
所以我知道
Which is how I knew
你会有此打算  里瑟先生
you'd put yourself in a situation like this, Mr. Reese.
站住别动
Stay where you are.
这里
Here.
查出硬盘里的内容  加以阻止
Find out what's on that hard drive and stop it.
你能否让我
Will you just let me--
你要做什么
What are you gonna do?
开枪吗
Shoot me?
这是我的过去导致的
This is my past catching up with me.
跟你没关系
It doesn't concern you.
现在有关系了
But this moment does.
我不会离开你  约翰
I'm not leaving you here, John.
所以我们别再浪费时间了好吗
So can we please stop wasting time?
看看情况如何
Let's see what we've got here.
你以前拆过炸弹背心吗
Have you ever defused a bomb vest before?
不能说拆过
Can't say I have.
不过我肯定明白基本原理
But I believe I grasp the basic principles.
我心甚慰啊
Well, that's encouraging.
她显然是用手机
It appears that she's wired the phone
作为触发器
to a capacitor-based trigger.
电话一打进来  就会触发电容器
If the phone is called, it will charge the capacitor
从而  进一步导致触发单一
which will, in turn, release it's charge in a single--
芬奇
Finch.
抱歉  积习难改
I'm sorry. This is my process.
能停掉计时器吗
Can you shut off the timer?
没法侵入电池系统
I can't get at the battery.
我需要黑到手机锁定码
I need to hack the phone's lock code.
能做到吗
Can you do it?
我造过有史以来最复杂的电脑系统
I have built some of the most complex computer systems in existence.
我肯定能解锁手机
I can certainly unlock a phone.
所有手机都有个通用的解锁码
All phones have a universal unlock code
基于其模式独一无二的手机串号
based on their model and the unique "IMEI" number.
好了
Okay.
对这部手机来说  是五个组合中的一个
For this phone, it's one of five combinations.
这挺好
That's good.
问题是我们只有三次尝试机会
The problem is we only get three attempts
然后手机就会永远锁定了
before the phone permanently locks us out.
这不好
That's not.
看来这个不对喽
I take it that one didn't do it?
抱歉
Sorry.
-你好  卡拉  -完成了
- Hello, Kara. - It's done.
是的
Yes.
我看到了  干得不错
So I see. Nicely done.
接下来交给我们
We'll take it from here.
现在我要你履行承诺
Now I want what you promised.
卖掉这台电脑
The person who sold the laptop
导致你中国不幸之旅的人
that took you on your unfortunate trip to China.
或者说幸运之旅  要看从谁的角度看了
Or fortunate, depending on one's view.
名字
The name.
恐怕我能给你的也只有名字
I'm afraid a name is all I have for you...
此人似乎在所有数据库中都不存在
for someone who seemingly does not exist on any known database.
也许你查起来会比我有运气
Perhaps you'll have better luck in your search than I did.
说吧
Go ahead.
怎么了
What?
你曾经说过
Something you said once.
迟早有一天  我们俩会死掉
About how sooner or later we'd both probably end up dead.
我喜欢迟点
I'd prefer later.
毕竟  最初是我把你拉进来的
After all, I'm the one that got you into this in the first place.
我很确定  如果不是你找到我  我已经死了
I'm pretty sure I'd be dead already if you hadn't found me.
难说
It's hard to say.
不难说
Not really.
选一个吧  哈罗德
Pick a winner, Harold.
你是对的  卡拉
You were right, Kara.
关于死  我特别擅长
About me being dead, I'm gonna be great at it.
肯定是哑弹
Must have been a dud.
看来斯诺还是退休了
Guess Snow retired after all.
乖
Boy.
警探
Detective?
摩斯特工
Agent Moss.
有何贵干
What brings you by?
我们辨认出了
We identified
国防部设施自杀炸弹客的身份
the suicide bombers who broke into the DOD facility.
是两位离队的中情局特工
Apparently they were a couple of rogue CIA agents.
中情局不肯吱声  不过我们认为他们是职业的
Agency's not saying a peep, but we think they went pro.
这一位  马克・斯诺
This one, Mark Snow,
很符合那位"西装男"的描述
fits the description of your "Man In A Suit".
真的吗
Really?
我们认为唐纳利去抓他们
We believe Donnelly was on to them.
他们发现了  杀死了他
They found out and killed him.
这么说局里
So does that mean the bureau's case
对西装男一案
against the man in the suit is--
正式结案
Closed officially.
至于唐纳利  我方会跟中情局沟通
As for Donnelly, we'll deal with the Agency on our end.
-保重  警探  -谢谢
- You take care, Detective. - Thank you.
还好吗
Everything okay?
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
硬盘有发现了吗
The hard drive tell you anything?
还没
Nothing yet.
她上传的东西  加密极为厉害
Whatever she uploaded, the encryption is remarkable.
我只能说此攻击软件
I can only assume that the malware
被保护到了极致
it's protecting is equally sophisticated.
我现在唯一能解码出的是
The only thing I've been able to decompile is
其上线时间距现在不足五个月了
when it's set to go live a little more than five months from now.
到时会发生什么
What happens then?
我想我们会发现的
I suppose we'll find out.
芬奇
Finch?
谢谢
Thank you.
拜托  不用说
Please, don't mention it.
2012年11月17日
恐怕我能给你的也只有名字
I'm afraid a name is all I have for you...
此人似乎在所有数据库中都不存在
for someone who seemingly does not exist on any known database.
也许你查起来会比我有运气
Perhaps you'll have better luck in your search than I did.
哈罗德
芬奇